<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>docker on urpylka՚s blog!</title>
    <link>https://urpylka.com/tags/docker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in docker on urpylka՚s blog!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Artem Smirnov</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 16:22:00 +0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://urpylka.com/tags/docker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CNCjs &#43; ESP-Link</title>
      <link>https://urpylka.com/posts/post-35/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 16:22:00 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://urpylka.com/posts/post-35/</guid>
      <description>Навигация по проекту:
 Покупка и разбор фрезерного станка Cutmaster CM-1500 Модернизация Cutmaster CM-1500 Установка и настройка Grbl CNCjs + ESP-Link Grbl + ESC &amp;amp; Brushless motor   Зачем нужен CNCjs? После замены компьютера на котором был Mach3 на Arduino, у станка не стало оконного интерфейса, взамен появился UART-интерфейс способный исполнять gcode-команды. Однако использовать терминал для управления станком не удобно. Нужен какой-то интерфейс, который позволит выполнять ручное управление станком (как пультом), а также позволит производить запуск управляющих программ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portainer: How to reset password for the Admin user</title>
      <link>https://urpylka.com/posts/post-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 23:30:00 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://urpylka.com/posts/post-18/</guid>
      <description>This article is a copy from the Portainer site. Original isn&amp;rsquo;t available anymore for unknown reasons, and I made it copy.
 Yep, we know, life can be challenging because you forgot or lost your Admin password to access to Portainer. In this help article, you will learn how to do a password reset to the Admin user of Portainer.
Resetting Admin password in Portainer running as container
Reset the password for the Admin user can be accomplished using our reset password container helper.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>