<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>programming on urpylka</title>
    <link>https://smirart.ru/tags/programming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in programming on urpylka</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Artem Smirnov</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 19:56:00 +0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://smirart.ru/tags/programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Платформа для собственного блога</title>
      <link>https://smirart.ru/posts/post-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 19:56:00 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://smirart.ru/posts/post-7/</guid>
      <description>Статья о том, какую платформу я выбрал для размещения собственного блога. Как я к этому пришёл и какие размышления у меня есть на счет дальнейшего развития этого направления.
 2013: Blogger История началась в февраля 2013 года. Я был студентом Аэрокоса (СГАУ – Самарский университет), и уже 4 года занимался веб-разработкой. Тогда мне пришла идея писать заметки. Делать это на собственной платформе вроде WordPress не хотелось, вполне изящным (на фоне Livejournal с его отвратительно перегруженным дизайном и рекламой во всех щелях) казалось решение от Google – платформа Blogger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheatsheet: Python</title>
      <link>https://smirart.ru/posts/post-89/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 12:35:00 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://smirart.ru/posts/post-89/</guid>
      <description>Everytime when I am doing a something by Python (or by something else) I need to use articles about main libraries. Despite that I&amp;rsquo;ve seen it a lot of times, it just can&amp;rsquo;t fit in my head. So I wrote this article to get the information quickly.
Basically it consist links to russian resources.
 os.path decorators strings regular expression queue, lock web, asyncio, aiohttp cycles, for, while   Maybe however I will write own copies of these scratches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nginx reverse proxy</title>
      <link>https://smirart.ru/posts/post-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://smirart.ru/posts/post-12/</guid>
      <description>Nginx reverse proxy needs where we want to get access to few resources by one external IP address and port.
I used that for several http web services (debian repository, my website and phpmyadmin). The following config is pairing server_name and proxy_pass as target location. Pleese look at last section with default_server atribute. It needs to set default site (in this case page with 501 Internal Error).
Quickstart   Create webproxy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>