<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>en on urpylka</title>
    <link>https://urpylka.com/tags/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in en on urpylka</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Artem Smirnov</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 23:30:00 +0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://urpylka.com/tags/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to reset password for the Admin user</title>
      <link>https://urpylka.com/posts/post-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 23:30:00 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://urpylka.com/posts/post-18/</guid>
      <description>This article is a copy from portainer site. Original isn&amp;rsquo;t available anymore for unknown reasons, and I made it copy.
 Yep, we know, life can be challenging because you forgot or lost your Admin password to access to Portainer. In this help article, you will learn how to do a password reset to the Admin user of Portainer.
Resetting Admin password in Portainer running as container
Reset the password for the Admin user can be accomplished using our reset password container helper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Postgres: Reset primary key sequence</title>
      <link>https://urpylka.com/posts/post-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 17:10:00 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://urpylka.com/posts/post-15/</guid>
      <description>Hello there!
I&amp;rsquo;ve met a problem with using SQLAlchemy framework. Look below:
db.session.add(AnObject) try: db.session.commit() except: db.session.rollback() An error in commit() cause the call to get a new sequence of the table primary key. It updates the sequence number like:
SELECT nextval(&amp;#39;table_id_seq&amp;#39;); I&amp;rsquo;d expected that rollback() must roll it back, but it didn&amp;rsquo;t. I tried to find solution at michaelcho.me but it was unsuccessful.
Solving First what may be found is the next command:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheatsheet: Python</title>
      <link>https://urpylka.com/posts/post-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 12:35:00 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://urpylka.com/posts/post-9/</guid>
      <description>Everytime when I am doing a something by Python (or by something else) I need to use articles about main libraries. Despite that I&amp;rsquo;ve seen it a lot of times, it just can&amp;rsquo;t fit in my head. So I wrote this article to get the information quickly.
Basically it consist links to russian resources.
 os.path decorators strings regular expression queue, lock web, asyncio, aiohttp cycles, for, while by value / by path list cycle for list remove spaces in a string low register in a string  Serial monitor on Python import serial port = serial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nginx reverse proxy</title>
      <link>https://urpylka.com/posts/post-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://urpylka.com/posts/post-12/</guid>
      <description>Nginx reverse proxy needs where we want to get access to few resources by one external IP address and port.
I used that for several http web services (debian repository, my website and phpmyadmin). The following config is pairing server_name and proxy_pass as target location. Pleese look at last section with default_server atribute. It needs to set default site (in this case page with 501 Internal Error).
Quickstart   Create webproxy.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>